發言。
立法會主席。
The first report.
和job seekers in recent years.
services in response to the changing needs of employer.
我有榮耀呈報我們的報告號碼72A。
which focus on the employment services provided by the labour department.
它 contains our conclusions and recommendations on the.
多謝主席。 on behalf of the public accounts committee.
chapter of planning, provision and management of public car park spaces.
This is the committee's second report on the director of audit report number seventy two.
was circulated to members in July and tabled in the council on 16 October this year.
石禮謙議員就政府賬目委員會第七十二號A報告書向本會發言，石禮謙議員。
I would like to take this opportunity to briefly recap the two main concerns of the committee on the employment services provided by the labour department.
The labour department is urged to conduct a comprehensive review to rationalise these services, with a view to meeting the needs of job seekers of different age groups.
The committee expresses grave concern and finds it unacceptable that the Labour Department had not proactively reviewed the modes in delivering its employment and recruitment.
forty-four thousand。
The shortage problem is getting worse in recent years.
Over the same period, the overall ratio of parking spaces to vehicle dropped.
The committee expresses grave concern and finds it unacceptable.
The labour department could not effectively assist this jobseekers in seeking jobs.
From 2006 to 2018, the total number of licensed commercial vehicles
而家，而
私家車和摩托車數增加44%，至約700和。
That some of the labour's department programmes specially designed for these job seekers were losing their attractiveness.
The job seekers with special needs, including ethnic minority job seekers, and job seekers with disabilities.
for the committee's present report number seventy two A, on planning, provision and management of public parking spaces.
From 1.32 to 1.02, and would further drop below one in the coming years, based on administration's projection.
The ratio for private cars decreased significantly in the same period, from 1.51 to 1.1, due to the substantial growth in the number of private cars.
委員會敦促勞動部加強協助就業人士有特殊需要者就業安置及留職安置的措施，以確保他們能夠在就業安置期間獲得適當的支持。
The committee notes that there have been a great concern among the public about the insufficient number of parking spaces for licensed vehicles, in particularly the private cars.
嗯。
committee。
until some 16 years.
質詢底行質詢張超雄議員。
later in two oh one eight that the transport department commissioned.
to make appropriate planning and to take timely measures to alleviate the shortage and shortfall of parking spaces for private cars.
The transport department is strongly urged to take appropriate measures to increase the supply of parking spaces to meet the widening shortfall.
這些 inadequacy have led to persistently insufficient supply of parking spaces to meet the parking demand of licensed vehicle.
The committee also expresses grave dismay and finds it unacceptable that the transport department, as the department responsible for the parking-related matters for licensed vehicles, have failed to make an
The committee strongly urges the transport department to closely monitor the progress of the pilot study and step up efforts in implementing this system. Lastly, I wish to record my appreciation of the contribution by members of the.
一consultant to conduct a pilot study on the feasibility of developing public car parks with such systems, and subject to the findings of the study, the construction of pilot projects in batches will only commence from two thousand and one.
The committee expresses grave dismay and finds it unacceptable about the inadequacies of the transport and housing bureau as the policy bureau on the subject in its long-term planning of car parking provision and in addressing the growth in the size of vehicle fleet.
The committee notes that the use of automatic automated parking system was one of the long-term remedial measures formulated in the administration's report on parking demand in two thousand and two to address the parking shortage. However, it was not an
Our gratitude goes to the witnesses who attended the hearing, helped by the committee. And I would like to express our gratitude to the director and his director of audit and his colleague for their unfailing support. Last but not the least, to the secretariat and clerk of the PAC. Thank you, Chairman.